## **NIKOLAI MAEV**

Yerevan, Armenia

trix.mnr@gmail.com — Skype: trix.mnr — Telegram: @trixon — linkedin.com/in/sharpdev/ — nickmaev.github.io

10 years experience in front- and back-end development with a vast array of knowledge in programming languages and tools. Design and development of the SaaP, SaaS practice. Complex problem-solving practice. Good cooperation skills.

# Experience

2020-08 -

Current

### Full Stack Engineer, ISDK, Moscow

C#, ASP.NET Core, NodeJS development. Setting up infrastructure using Microsoft Azure. Setting up intra-corporate pipelines using Docker, Linux and Jenkins. Application, database design and development. Front-end design and development with TypeScript, React, Redux. Team management, staff training, code reviewing.

2016-05 -

2020-07

### Full Stack Engineer, StecPoint, Moscow

C#, ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Core development. Application, database design and development. Development using microservices. Front-end design and development with TypeScript, React, Redux. Team management, staff training, code reviewing.

2013-07 -

2016-03

#### Full Stack Developer, S4AB, Rostov-on-Don

C#, ASP.NET MVC full-stack development with JavaScript, jQuery. Database design.

#### Education

2007-09 -

2013-07

The specialist-level degree (eq. to Master's degree) in Radiophysics and electronics, Southern Federal University, Rostov-on-Don

Defending a thesis related to digital signal processing.

#### Skills

.NET

Docker

JavaScript

Jenkins

• C#

PostgreSQL

React

Azure

ASP.NET Core

Linux

Redux

xUnit

NodeJS

TypeScript

WebPack

NextJS

#### **Activities**

Creator and main contributor of the several opensource projects which are aimed to construct stable web applications using the most popular programming technologies.

## Languages

English B2, Russian C2